<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="appcirculate_fragment_circulate_device_card_switch_title_1">Turn on WLAN and Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="appcirculate_fragment_circulate_device_card_switch_title_3">Turn on WLAN</string>
    <string name="appcirculate_toast_cancel">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="camera_choose_device">Switch cameras</string>
    <string name="car_card_seat_back_middle_seat">Centre (back)</string>
    <string name="circulate_card_mirror_device_button">Abort</string>
    <string name="circulate_card_sticker_dressing_equipment">Customise device</string>
    <string name="circulate_card_sticker_expend_contentDescription">Show customised devices</string>
    <string name="circulate_cta_premission_wlan_subtitle_china">For transferring items and connecting devices via WLAN</string>
    <string name="circulate_jump_to_mijia">Open Mi Home</string>
    <string name="circulate_pad_card_being_used_cellular_wifi_china">WLAN signal shared with tablet</string>
    <string name="circulate_phone_card_using_cellular_wifi_china">"Using phone's WLAN signal"</string>
    <string name="circulate_title">Xiaomi Smart Hub</string>
    <string name="close_auxiliary_wifi_hint_china">Turn off \"Dual band WLAN speed boost\" to be able to cast</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_label_china">Xiaomi Conference Tapcast WLAN</string>
    <string name="connect_settings_summary_global">Discover nearby devices signed in to your Xiaomi Account and add them to Xiaomi Smart Hub</string>
    <string name="console_guide_subtitle_small_window">"Minimise the window that's being cast to be able to use other features of your phone"</string>
    <string name="dialog_connect_verify_perssion">Authorise casting on your TV first</string>
    <string name="dialog_connect_verify_perssion_fail">"Couldn't authorise casting on your TV. Wait a minute or two and try again."</string>
    <string name="dialog_nfc_cast_wifi_off">Turn on WLAN to be able to cast using NFC. Turn on now?</string>
    <string name="dialog_scan_message_china">"%1$d. Connect both your mobile device and TV to the same WLAN network.

%2$d. View \"Help\" to learn more."</string>
    <string name="dialog_scanning_close_dual_wifi_china">Turn off \"Dual band WLAN speed boost\" to be able to cast. Turn this feature off now?</string>
    <string name="dialog_scanning_precondition_new_china">Turn on WLAN, Bluetooth, and location services to be able to use casting. Turn on now?</string>
    <string name="dual_wifi_warning_china">Turn off dual WLAN and try again</string>
    <string name="err_toast_msg_try_switch_network">Connect both your mobile device and computer to the same WLAN network</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_month_day">M-d</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_year_month">M-yyyy</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_year_month_day">M-d-yyyy</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour">"H 'o''clock'"</string>
    <string name="global_privacy_feature">Using minimised windows, casting with the screen off, and hiding private items.</string>
    <string name="global_privacy_tip"><Data>We need to collect necessary personal information to provide you with the basic services and optimise the casting process. You can learn how we handle the information we collect in our &lt;a href=%1$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>. You can withdraw your consent to the Privacy Policy in the Settings at any time.</Data></string>
    <string name="help_page_text_06">"%1$d. Xiaomi TVs, set-top boxes, projectors:
Connect both your mobile device and external monitor to the same WLAN network for best effect. If they are connected to different networks, it might take more time to find the external monitor and connect.
Note: Older TV models might not support casting across different networks.
%2$d. If you're using TVs, set-top boxes, or projectors of other brands, connect both your mobile device and external monitor to the same WLAN network.
If the two devices can't be connected to the same network, turn on Miracast on your external monitor. The naming of Miracast functionality might vary."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_06_new_2">"%1$d. Make sure your mobile device and external monitor are connected to the same Wi-Fi network.
%2$d. On some Xiaomi TVs, you can set up casting from the TV as well as customise device search and verification methods."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_09">"Tap the \"Cast\" toggle on your phone's Notification shade. Turn on both WLAN and Bluetooth for a more stable connection."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_09_new_1">"Turn on casting in your device's Control centre, then search for an external monitor."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_17">"You can project items from your Xiaomi phone on most Xiaomi TV models with Bluetooth capabilities without turning on Miracast manually.
If you need to turn on Miracast, press the [MENU] button and select My apps > Casting > Miracast."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_37">First, make sure that Miracast functionality is supported on your device. On some of the models, you can press the [SOURCE] button on the remote control and then select \"Screen Mirroring\". On some other models, you can turn this feature on in Networks > WLAN Direct. This feature is turned on by default on various models.</string>
    <string name="preference_copied">"'%1$s' copied to clipboard."</string>
    <string name="privacy_permission_wlan_china">Turning WLAN on and off</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_device_dialog_message">"If you turn this feature on, you'll be able to discover nearby TVs, speakers, and cars in Control centre. Turn on now?"</string>
    <string name="scan_wifi_label_china">Connect to WLAN</string>
    <string name="screen_projection_characteristics_small_window_summary">"Minimise the window that's being cast to be able to use other features of your phone."</string>
    <string name="screen_projection_characteristics_small_window_title">Minimise window</string>
    <string name="small_window">Minimise window</string>
    <string name="small_window_not_supported">"Can't minimise this app while it's being cast"</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_for_small_window">"You can minimise the window that's being cast to be able to use other features of your phone without interrupting the casting process."</string>
    <string name="toast_title_for_small_window">Select \"Minimise window\" in the app</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_device_message_china"><Data>&lt;xliff:g id=count refersto=1>%1$d&lt;/xliff:g>. Connect both your mobile device and TV to the same WLAN network.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;xliff:g id=count refersto=2>%2$d&lt;/xliff:g>. On some TV models, this feature is only available when screen mirroring is on. View &lt;a href=milink://com.milink.service/specification>\"Help\"&lt;/a> to learn more.</Data></string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute">H:mm</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute_second">H:mm:ss</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute_second_millis">H:mm:ss.S</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_16">Xiaomi TV/Mi Projector</string>
    <string name="appcirculate_toast_app_notstall">"Couldn't transfer. This app isn't installed on the phone."</string>
    <string name="circulate_cta_premission_wlan_title">开启或关闭WLAN</string>
    <string name="circulate_cta_user_agreement">Read and agree to our &lt;txt href=\"%1$s\">User Agreement&lt;/txt> and &lt;txt href=\"%2$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/txt> before you continue.</string>
    <string name="circulate_more_button_content_description">More</string>
    <string name="connect_settings_presentation_password_error">Incorrect password</string>
    <string name="connect_settings_presentation_password_title">Enter admin password</string>
    <string name="message_connection_interrupted">Make sure your computer and tablet are within connection range and have Bluetooth and WLAN turned on. To continue, start the task on your computer again.</string>
</resources>
