<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Settings_title_power_center">Battery optimisation settings</string>
    <string name="action_button_text_100">Optimise</string>
    <string name="action_button_text_80_100">Optimise</string>
    <string name="activity_title_power_manager">Battery optimisation</string>
    <string name="antivirus_privacy_dialog_cloudscan_description">"To detect and neutralise viruses more effectively, we'll upload the apps' package names and properties in order to scan them using a cloud engine."</string>
    <string name="antivirus_privacy_dialog_summary">&lt;Data>This feature is powered by a third party antivirus engine. To learn more, read the &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">License Agreement&lt;/a> provided by the third party.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="antivirus_privacy_dialog_summary_kddi">"&lt;Data>When you're performing a security scan, your device model and scan results will be uploaded to %1$s servers and used in accordance with the corresponding &lt;a href=\"%2$s\">terms and conditions&lt;/a>.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>Read and agree to %3$s's terms and conditions before performing security scans.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>If you don't agree to upload data to %4$s servers, you can still use the virus definitions stored locally on your device.&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_about_content_no_link">"The system can show when apps launched other apps, autostarted, used permissions, and performed sensitive actions. Due to Android version compatibility issues, some of these records might not be accurate. If you find an app behaviour record that isn't accurate, report it to us using the \"Services &amp; feedback\" app."</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_door">App behaviour records</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_header_time">dd MMMM</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_menu_about">About app behaviour records</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_record_close_title">Turning off records</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_record_open_content_text">Turn on app behaviour records to understand how apps use your personal information.</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_record_setting_button_title">Show behaviour of system services</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_record_setting_show_system_desc">"Turn on to view the behaviour of basic system services. To ensure the stability of the system, these services will use the required permissions some of which can't be restricted."</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_record_setting_show_system_title">Show behaviour of system services</string>
    <string name="app_behavior_record_setting_title">Behaviour records</string>
    <string name="app_management_for_independent_storage">Isolate cached data</string>
    <string name="app_management_for_independent_storage_desc">Only allow the app to access its own files and data</string>
    <string name="app_manager_anomaly_analysis">Analyse third party app problems</string>
    <string name="app_manager_as_dlg_msg_new">"Allowing an app to autostart may increase the amount of memory and battery life it uses. Your device will optimise the autostart permissions of apps you don't use frequently to improve performance."</string>
    <string name="auto_start_tips">"This feature will optimise the autostart permissions of apps you don't use frequently to improve device performance."</string>
    <string name="auto_task_edit_operation_summary">For example, \"Turn on Aeroplane mode\"</string>
    <string name="auto_task_notify_task_cancel_count_down_new">Automated action will be cancelled in %d seconds</string>
    <string name="auto_task_notify_task_canceled_summary3">Cancelled by Second space</string>
    <string name="auto_task_notify_task_canceled_summary4">Cancelled by First space</string>
    <string name="auto_task_notify_task_canceled_title">Action is cancelled</string>
    <string name="auto_task_operation_airplane_mode">Aeroplane mode</string>
    <string name="back_sound_support_china">Turn off WLAN first</string>
    <string name="beauty_portrait_center_desc">Automatically identify and centre faces in video calls and meetings. This feature is not supported by some apps.</string>
    <string name="bh_product_status_abnormal_phone_text">"Couldn't recognise phone number."</string>
    <string name="blur_key_words_permission_records">App behaviour records</string>
    <string name="btn_text_optimize_manually">Optimise manually</string>
    <string name="btn_text_optimize_now">Optimise</string>
    <string name="bubble_mode_barrage_switch_tips">Turn on to show conversation bubbles for minimised apps as on-screen comments</string>
    <string name="bubble_mode_barrage_tips">Conversation bubbles for minimised apps will be shown as on-screen comments</string>
    <string name="cs_color_sense">Colour temperature</string>
    <string name="cta_main_purpose">"Welcome to Security! You can use Security and its modules (including system security components, system services, Joyose, and Cleaner) to free up storage space, scan your device for viruses, control battery usage, optimise your device for gaming, manage apps, receive earthquake early warnings, and more. System security components will connect to the internet and perform security scans while you're installing apps and making payments."</string>
    <string name="cta_main_purpose_new">"Welcome to Security! You can use Security and its modules (including system security components, security and system services, Joyose, and Cleaner) to free up storage space, scan your device for viruses, control battery usage, optimise your device for gaming, manage apps, receive earthquake early warnings, and more. System security components will connect to the internet and perform security scans while you're installing apps and making payments."</string>
    <string name="custom_define_permission_desc_android.permission.READ_SMS">For using blocklist and recognising messages from your carrier</string>
    <string name="custom_define_permission_desc_android.permission_group.LOCATION">For providing the features relevant to your location in Warning Centre, Emergency SOS, App battery saver, payment security scanner, and approximate location service</string>
    <string name="data_booster_title">Stabilise data connection</string>
    <string name="delete">Remove</string>
    <string name="descx_quick_scan_cancel">Scan cancelled</string>
    <string name="dialog_app_roaming_message">"%1$s can't use mobile data when roaming. When you're roaming, only apps you've added to exceptions can use mobile data."</string>
    <string name="dialog_app_roaming_title">"%1$s can't use data roaming"</string>
    <string name="dialog_roaming_message">Your carrier may charge you additional fees for using data while roaming.</string>
    <string name="dialog_roaming_title">Allow data roaming?</string>
    <string name="disable_air_mode">Turn Aeroplane mode off first</string>
    <string name="doze_optimization_title">Optimised touch controls</string>
    <string name="examination_score_80_100">A few items can be optimised</string>
    <string name="examination_score_80_60">Some items can be optimised</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_garbage_clean_message_new">&lt;Data>Cleaner can free up &lt;font color=#0099ff>%s&lt;/font> of storage space. Clean now?&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_homepage_optimise_message">"Your device's performance score is lower than 80 points. Optimise now?"</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_release_memory_title_new">&lt;Data>Speed up your device by &lt;font color=#0099ff>%s&lt;/font>&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_scan_message">"Your device's performance score is lower than 75 points. Optimise now?"</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_scan_positive_button">Optimise</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_scan_title">Optimise performance</string>
    <string name="exo_controls_fastforward_description">Fast-forward</string>
    <string name="exo_download_paused_for_wifi">Downloads waiting for Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="exo_track_role_alternate">Alternative</string>
    <string name="face_unlock_check_failed">"Couldn't recognise you"</string>
    <string name="face_unlock_not_found">"Couldn't recognise you"</string>
    <string name="face_unlock_verity_dialog_title_failed">"Couldn't recognise you"</string>
    <string name="firewall_activity_lable">Restrict data usage by app</string>
    <string name="firewall_system_title">System app connections</string>
    <string name="first_aid_card_airplane_summary">Turn off Aeroplane mode to be able to make calls and connect to the network</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_month_day">M-d</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_year_month">M-yyyy</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_year_month_day">M-d-yyyy</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour">"H 'o''clock'"</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute">H:mm</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute_second">H:mm:ss</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute_second_millis">H:mm:ss.S</string>
    <string name="freeform_vedio_description_open_freeform_and_splitscreen">"· Tap an app on the sidebar to open it in a floating window.
· Drag an app to the centre of the screen to open it in a floating window or to the side to use Split screen."</string>
    <string name="game_performance_wild_mode">Ultimate mode</string>
    <string name="gb_adv_touch_custom_title">Customise</string>
    <string name="gb_game_ratio_center">Centre</string>
    <string name="gb_performace_guide_disable_desc">"&lt;Data>Can't switch to Balanced mode in Game Turbo when system-wide Performance mode is on. You can change battery settings in Security.&lt;br>&lt;a href=\"#\">Open Security&lt;/a>&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="gb_performance_enhance_sub_title">Prioritise performance over power consumption</string>
    <string name="gb_predownload_dialog_message_china">"&lt;Data>Updated content for this game can be downloaded to this device automatically after you connect to WLAN and turn the screen off. Thus, you'll be able to use the new version as soon as it's released.&lt;br>&lt;br>Read and agree to the &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Statement on background updates&lt;/a> before using this feature.&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="gb_shoulder_key_light_effect">Colour animations</string>
    <string name="gb_shoulder_key_light_effect_subtitle">"Colour animations will be displayed when pop-up triggers are on and you're playing games"</string>
    <string name="gd_setting_group_custom_settings">Personalisation</string>
    <string name="gdpr_msg">"&lt;Data>To be able to detect security risks and protect your data, we need to collect the necessary amount of information about your device. Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"https://privacy.mi.com/all/%1$s_%2$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before using our services. In case you don't allow us to collect such information, you'll still be able to use this app, but some features won't be available to you. &lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="global_dock_guide_desc_with_split_screen">"· Tap an app on the sidebar to open it in a floating window.
· Drag an app to the centre of the screen to open it in a floating window or to the side to use Split screen.
· Press and hold the indicator to move the window around."</string>
    <string name="gs_auto_clean_memory_detail">Clear cache automatically to optimise gaming</string>
    <string name="gs_performance_mode_detail">Optimise system performance for gaming</string>
    <string name="gtb_dialog_privacy_speed_tips">"&lt;Data>I've read and agreed to Xunyou Game Booster &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy.&lt;/a>&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="gtb_dialog_privacy_voice_tips">"&lt;Data>I've read and agreed to Xunyou Game Voice Changer &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy.&lt;/a>&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="gtb_dialog_title_smart_5g">5G network optimisation</string>
    <string name="gtb_guide_accelerate">Tap \"Boost\" to optimise your gaming</string>
    <string name="gtb_guide_accelerated_tips">Game Turbo is optimising your gaming experience now</string>
    <string name="gtb_guide_gtb_line_wilde_mode">Try Ultimate mode in Game Turbo to take your gaming to the next level</string>
    <string name="gtb_setting_item_title_smart_5g">5G network optimisation</string>
    <string name="hide_mode_result_summary_text">Customise Battery saver settings for individual apps</string>
    <string name="international_roaming_setting">Data roaming</string>
    <string name="last_check_canceled">Previous scan was cancelled</string>
    <string name="lockpattern_access_need_to_unlock_wrong_fingerprint">"Couldn't recognise fingerprint, try again."</string>
    <string name="manual_item_white_list_summary">Prevent selected items from being optimised</string>
    <string name="menu_item_control_app_permissions">Ask your permission before allowing apps to read your contacts, view your call history, change system settings or access camera and other device resources</string>
    <string name="menu_item_notification_power_text">Battery optimisation</string>
    <string name="menu_item_shortcut_summary">Place features on your home screen</string>
    <string name="mi_ime_not_used">Use a keyboard authorised by Xiaomi</string>
    <string name="miui_optimization_close_final_tip">Turn off system optimisation?</string>
    <string name="miui_optimization_close_title">This feature is intended for developers and might not be convenient for general users. Turning off system optimisation might bring about the following changes:</string>
    <string name="nd_result_button_optimize">Optimise</string>
    <string name="nd_result_summary_optimize">"Try optimising network connection when it's unstable"</string>
    <string name="nd_result_title_optimize">Network optimisation</string>
    <string name="network_assistant_privacy">To keep track of data usage by app, we collect information such as package names, WLAN and mobile data usage, peak and off-peak data usage, and when WLAN and mobile data is on. This information is stored locally on your device.</string>
    <string name="notification_antivirus_message">Scan now to neutralise risks</string>
    <string name="notify_channel_name_behavior">Behaviour history</string>
    <string name="oaid_tips_content">Virtual IDs (OAID) can be used for tracking your behaviour and personalising ads for you. You can select which apps are allowed to access your virtual ID. Note that if you restrict access, ad recommendations might become irrelevant or apps might not be able to work normally.</string>
    <string name="operator_location_settings_message">"Couldn't recognise your carrier and location. Can't set phone balance and data usage warnings now."</string>
    <string name="optmizingbar_optimize_done">Optimised</string>
    <string name="optmizingbar_ready">Optimising…</string>
    <string name="optmizingbar_title_acceleration">Optimising…</string>
    <string name="organization">Organisation</string>
    <string name="pc_activity_title">Optimise battery</string>
    <string name="pc_fast_charge_switch_summary">"Turn on to speed up the charging process. This feature will prioritise charging speed while ensuring your device's safety. The lower your battery is, the faster it will be charged. This feature might heat up your device."</string>
    <string name="pc_intellect_charge_protect_title">Optimised charging</string>
    <string name="pc_wireless_handle_title">Camera grip</string>
    <string name="perfermance_optimization_title">Performance optimisation</string>
    <string name="permission_close_permission_control_dialog_msg">"When permission manager is off, apps won't ask your permission before reading your contacts, viewing your call history, changing system settings or accessing camera and other device resources."</string>
    <string name="permission_instruction_shake">"This permission allows apps to detect the device's position in space, recognise shaking, and determine screen orientation."</string>
    <string name="permission_permission_control_closed_desc_dialog_msg">"Apps won't ask your permission before reading your contacts, viewing your call history, changing system settings or accessing camera and other device resources. You can turn this feature on in Permission settings."</string>
    <string name="permission_with_call_and_contact">Permissions related to phone calls, contact info and call history.</string>
    <string name="phone_manage_electric_summary">Optimise your device to save battery</string>
    <string name="power_btn_analyze">Analyse battery usage</string>
    <string name="power_center_battery_health_poor_tip">Looks like battery health is low. Check your battery in an authorised service centre.</string>
    <string name="power_center_dialog_msg_top">When Battery saver is on, the following optimisations will be performed:</string>
    <string name="power_center_night_charge_noti_title">Optimised charging is on</string>
    <string name="power_center_night_charge_protection">Optimised charging</string>
    <string name="power_center_one_key_save">Optimise</string>
    <string name="power_center_speed_mode_summary">Prioritise performance over power consumption and temperature control</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_button">Find an authorised service provider</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_dialog">Unauthorised battery warning</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_dialog_summary">Looks like an unauthorised battery is installed in this device. Charging power will be lowered to protect your device. Using unauthorised batteries may result in battery swelling, overheating, and leakage. It may also cause fire or other hazards. Find an authorised service provider to replace your battery.</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_summary1">This device was equipped with a built-in battery that should only be replaced by an authorised service provider.</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_summary2">Replacing the battery elsewhere may damage this device. Using unauthorised batteries may result in battery swelling, overheating, and leakage. It may also cause fire or other hazards. Do not use unauthorised batteries.</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_tip">"Health info isn't available for this unauthorised battery. Tap to learn about security risks."</string>
    <string name="power_center_unoffical_battery_title">Risks caused by using unauthorised batteries</string>
    <string name="power_dailog_night_charge_protection_summary">Looks like your battery is fully charged most of the time, which may speed up its aging. Optimised charging is now turned on to avoid such problems.</string>
    <string name="power_optimize_battery_save_idea">Optimise battery</string>
    <string name="power_optimize_btn_text_fixed">Optimised</string>
    <string name="power_optimize_catagory_fixed_title">Optimised</string>
    <string name="power_optimize_darkmode_dialog_summary">Dark mode changes the colour scheme of the system UI and selected apps allowing you to save battery and reduce eye strain.</string>
    <string name="power_optimize_darkmode_extend_summary">Dark mode changes the colour scheme of the system UI and selected apps allowing you to save battery and reduce eye strain</string>
    <string name="power_optimize_power_save_summary">Turn on Battery saver to apply multiple system optimisations that limit background activity</string>
    <string name="power_save_mode_other_optimization">Optional optimisation</string>
    <string name="power_save_started_summary_text">"Battery saver is on. It reduces apps' background activity, stops sync, and minimises system animations."</string>
    <string name="power_save_summary_text">"Turn on Battery saver to reduce apps' background activity, stop sync, and minimise system animations."</string>
    <string name="power_setting_power_save_summary_text">Optimise system settings to save battery</string>
    <string name="power_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_allow_connect_network_title">International roaming</string>
    <string name="preference_copied">"'%1$s' copied to clipboard."</string>
    <string name="privacy_app_behavior_title">App behaviour history</string>
    <string name="privacy_dialog_content_part2">&lt;Data>Security needs to collect necessary personal information to provide you with its services and be able to improve its features. You can learn how we handle the information we collect in our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a>. You can withdraw your consent to the Privacy Policy of Security in the Settings at any time.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="privacy_dialog_content_part3">"&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%2$s\">User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before using Security. If you don't agree to use the aforementioned services, you won't be able to use some features of this app; however, its basic functionality will still be available to you.&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="privacy_dialog_danger_mission_message">Android has multiple high-risk permissions (e.g. the permission to send you push notifications). To protect your privacy, the system will ask whether you allow such behaviour, and provide restriction options.</string>
    <string name="privacy_flares_behavior_recent">App behaviour</string>
    <string name="privacy_mask_summary">Instead of your real identifier, the system will provide a virtual ID (OAID) to third party apps. It prevents apps from tracking your behaviour and preferences and protects your privacy.</string>
    <string name="privacy_provision_text">We are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Prioritising research and development in the field of information security, Xiaomi constantly works on improving the methods, practices, and technical solutions that safeguard your data. We also share our latest achievements with our partners in order to ensure your privacy across the board.</string>
    <string name="privacy_recommend_category">Personalisation</string>
    <string name="privacy_recommend_summary">Receive personalised content recommendations</string>
    <string name="privacy_recommend_title">Personalised recommendations</string>
    <string name="privacy_revoke_category_title">Withdrawal of consent and service cancellation</string>
    <string name="privacy_revoke_tip_dialog_content">"&lt;Data>You won't be able to keep using %1$s unless you agree to the new version of its Privacy Policy. Agree to the updated %2$s &lt;a href=\"%3$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> now?&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="privacy_search_key_4">App behaviour</string>
    <string name="privacy_thumbnail_blur_title">Blur previews</string>
    <string name="privacy_update_dialog_content_2">&lt;Data>Read and agree to the new version of &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="risk_app_install_auth_result">"You've authorised installing %1$s. You can continue once the installation package is detected."</string>
    <string name="risk_app_install_history">Authorisation history</string>
    <string name="roaming_not_start_title">Data roaming</string>
    <string name="roaming_start_title">Data roaming</string>
    <string name="scan_open_shut_down_password_content">Protect your device from unauthorised access</string>
    <string name="security_scan_optimizing">Optimising…</string>
    <string name="setting_wireless_reverse_charging_summary">Place the device that supports Qi wireless charging (e.g. phone or wearable device) on the centre of the back of this device</string>
    <string name="shutdown_cancel_reminder_detail2">"Looks like you're playing a game now. Scheduled power off is cancelled."</string>
    <string name="sp_micare_title">Warning Centre</string>
    <string name="special_perm_intercept_action_title">Learn your behaviour and automate actions</string>
    <string name="special_perm_intercept_analyze_title">Analyse your preferences and behaviour</string>
    <string name="special_perm_power_msg">Allow apps to optimise battery usage in the background</string>
    <string name="special_perm_power_title">Optimise battery usage</string>
    <string name="storage_fbo_tools">Storage optimisation</string>
    <string name="storage_fob_date_format">dd/MM</string>
    <string name="storage_ufs_msg">You can add up to %1$s of storage to this device using our UFS storage extension technology and storage optimisation algorithms.</string>
    <string name="summary_safe_mode">Neutralise risks during installation</string>
    <string name="superpower_notification_time_12">EEEE, dd MMMM</string>
    <string name="superpower_notification_time_24">EEEE, dd MMMM</string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_analytics_declare">"We invite you to enroll in our User Experience Programme. This app needs to connect to the Internet and use the following permissions or features to collect stats in order to improve the services we provide to you. We collect data here only for statistical purposes, and we can't identify you personally based on the data we collect."</string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_double_link">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href=\"%2$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_meanwhile_double_link">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href=\"%2$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_meanwhile_privacy_policy">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_meanwhile_user_agreement">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">User Agreement&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_no_say_no_analytics">"If you don't want to grant these permissions, you can unenroll in Settings > Additional settings > Privacy > User Experience Programme."</string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_privacy_policy">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_revoke_uninstallable">You can sign out, uninstall this app, or revoke your authorisation in Security > Manage apps > Permissions > Permissions.</string>
    <string name="system_permission_declare_user_agreement">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=\"%1$s\">User Agreement&lt;/a> before you continue.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="tc_sms_report_notify_correction_body">Go to the Data usage app in Security Centre and try again manually.</string>
    <string name="title_eye_shield">"Screen colour doesn't look right?"</string>
    <string name="vb_movie_mode">Theatre mode</string>
    <string name="vb_movie_power_hint">"Theatre mode provides an immersive viewing experience.
Your device might heat up and consume more power."</string>
    <string name="vb_quick_func_auto_bgm">Recognise background music</string>
    <string name="vb_theatre_switch_guide">Tap to switch to Theatre mode</string>
    <string name="vb_voice_adjust">Theatre audio</string>
    <string name="virus_ignore_dialog_content">"If you choose to ignore possible risks posed by an app, you'll no longer be notified about them. However, you should remember that it doesn't mean such risks are neutralised."</string>
    <string name="vtb_func_display_style_desc0">AI can recognise people, animals, plants, sky, buildings, and other objects featured in videos and dynamically enhance them.</string>
    <string name="wlan_booster">Wi-Fi optimisation</string>
    <string name="wlan_optimization_title">Wi-Fi optimisation</string>
    <string name="gb_barrage_chat_text_color">Colour</string>
    <string name="gb_collimator_color">Colour</string>
    <string name="gb_shoulder_key_light_effect_color">Colour</string>
</resources>
